gitBranchingExercise

To create a branch:
git branch BranchName

fast-forward vs recursive
fast-forward is the simple merge that can be done when the branch is simply
an addition to the main branch. recursive is used when both branches have
new commits

to switch to another branch
git checkout BranchName

to delete a branch
git branch -d BranchName

merge conflits happen when the same file is edited on two different branches 
and attemped to be merged together. Git cannot know which version of the file 
to use, so the user must correct the conflict before merging 